Taichi!
Hey.
You didn't need to run all the way to school, you know.
But... the text you sent... said that you wanted to talk.
Nagase...
After a lot of thinking, I've come to realize that I'm a really self-centered and stubborn person.
When I think something has to be a certain way, I won't listen to reason
and always try to get my way.
And when I think I'm right, I try to force everyone to believe that I am.
That's why I ended up hurting Inaba, fighting with Aoki...
and hurting you, too.
I'm just a selfish person.
That's why I tried to put some distance between us. I didn't want to hurt anyone.
But after distancing myself from you all,
I realized that I really want to be with everyone.
I realized that I'd rather be with you and hurt you than stay apart and not hurt you.
So if you don't mind,
can I stay by your side?
That's so mean, Taichi!
Um... Uh...
I tried so hard to keep us together.
But if we're only going to get hurt, we may need to be apart, after all.
I thought so, too.
But now you're saying that we need to hurt each other?
Will that really work?
Well, I guess it can.
I never thought I'd ever hear you say that we'd need to hurt each other.
Well, I did give it a lot of thought.
Are you going to tell everyone else something similar to what you just told me
and get us all back together?
That's the plan.
It just doesn't feel right.
I try so hard, then you swoop in and take all the glory.
Well...
I agree with you.
You're selfish.
But you know, I think you're doing the right thing,
even if there are better ways for you to go about it.
My sister says the same thing.
So I'm sorry I pushed you—
Didn't you just say that sometimes we'd need to hurt each other?
This is a different kind of "hurt," though.
It's okay.
I already told you that.
I'm going to talk to Inaban first.
I'll see if I can get a hold of Aoki.
Okay! Let's do this!
Yeah!
It feels like we haven't talked in ages.
Yeah.
Listen, Aoki.
I said something really mean the other day.
I was cocky and full of myself.
I thought I could do anything.
But I was wrong.
I can't undo what I did, but I can at least apologize.
I'm really sorry.
Ao—
Dammit, what the hell?!
I knew you'd beat me to it!
You see, I really wanted to apologize, too.
But I knew you beat me to it as soon as you called.
Iori-chan telling me to stop being jealous hit me pretty hard.
Like a knife through the chest.
But it didn't hurt because it was mean.
It hurt because it was true.
I was jealous of you because you saved Yui and everyone else, while I couldn't do anything.
I was in denial and just couldn't admit it.
It was nothing more than luck.
And when all is said and done, I saved them for my own selfish reasons.
Taichi,
I'm really sorry, too!
Aoki...
Can I come in now?
I see. So it didn't work.
She went home before I could talk to her.
But I think I'll go to her house later today.
It'd probably be a bad idea for all of us to go.
Think Inaba-chan let Iori-chan in?
She said she'd call if things went well.
She hasn't called yet, so...
Taichi.
Let's sit down for a bit.
Talking man-to-man in a place like this is like youth at full throttle!
Let's youth it up!
It might be impossible to do stuff for others without thinking about what's in it for ourselves.
Yeah. Maybe it's all about yourself in the end.
But...
You want to save Yui, right?
Just us wanting her to come out isn't enough.
She needs to want to come out, too.
But we don't know when this whole thing will end.
We can't let her stay in her room forever.
Maybe we could stay near Kiriyama and stop her if her desires were to get unleashed.
Do you really think we could stop her?
If we're really careful and don't back down...
That's like something our grandparents would say...
How'd you think of doing that to help her get over her trauma, anyway?
The idea came from something you said.
There were some things we could only do because our personalities were switching.
That's how I got the idea.
So maybe there's something we can only do because our desires are being unleashed.
I think I got it.
Seriously?
Yui! Yui!
Your friends are here to see you.
Open the door, Yui.
Don't worry, Mother!
We can handle things from here!
I'm so sorry.
You go through so much trouble for my daughter.
Not at all! It's because it's for your daughter!
Yui, it's me and Taichi.
We need to talk. Could you open the door?
It's open.
It's been... a while.
Yui, let's go outside.
Let's go to school. You'll be fine.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't know when or if I'll hit someone.
I can't go outside.
But if you keep shutting yourself in like this, it could go on forever.
You'll be fine! I know it!
You'll be able to hold back if you—
Don't lie to me!
Even if I don't want to, if my desires get unleashed, I'll do it anyway!
I know you won't!
Even if your desires get unleashed,
if you really, honestly, absolutely don't want to do it, you won't do it!
None of that matters when your desires get unleashed.
Whether you want to stop or not won't matter.
That's how it works, right?
That's how it works, but that's not how it works!
What?
If you really don't want to do it, you won't do it!
If I can prove that to you, you'll go outside, come to school, and return to the club room, right?
Well, if you can prove that I won't do it, then...
All right! Perfect!
Not to brag, but I love you, Yui.
I really love you!
I'll love you forever!
With every fiber of my being!
And not to brag, but I've got a dirty mind.
It's really dirty.
Insanely dirty.
One hell of a dirty mind!
What's your point?
And right now, our desires are getting unleashed.
In other words, there's no telling when I'm going to assault you.
Wh-What the heck are you saying?!
Gross!
W-Wait! That's not what I meant!
What I'm saying is, I can prove that I can win against my desires through willpower!
You freak!
I'll prove that you can stop yourself from doing something you really don't want to!
Wh-What is wrong with you?!
You're not making any sense!
Well, you kind of do, but...
Right?
So, Yui...
Let's go to a love hotel.
No!
Why would I go to a place like that and put myself in danger?!
You won't be in any danger.
How can you say that?!
Because hurting you is the one thing I never, ever want to do.
Because I love you.
Hurting you is the last thing I'd want to do.
I know it won't happen, but if I do lose to my desires,
you can totally beat the crap out of me.
Don't say that.
I don't want to hurt you.
And just for good measure, you should wear something erotic.
Like just your underwear, or a bunny girl outfit, or nothing but an apron—
Stop imagining things like that, you creep!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Okay, Taichi. Let's end this with a baseless claim.
Don't call it baseless before I make it!
You two are just so... stupid.
So let's hear this baseless claim.
Don't you call it baseless, too!
Anyway, I've been wondering.
Before you went berserk at the station,
had you ever really gotten violent and injured anyone?
Well, when I practiced karate, I did a few times.
But that's not really being violent.
I mean, it was during practice and matches.
I thought so.
That means that you didn't know what it really meant to hurt someone, right?
But you know exactly what it means now.
And you don't want to hurt anyone again.
That means that even if you want to beat someone to a pulp,
your desire not to hurt them might be stronger.
Well, if you can call something like that a desire, too...
Actually, I injured Nagase when my desires got unleashed the other day.
So I think I kind of know how you feel.
But I still want to be with everyone.
Don't you feel the same way?
Why not put some more faith in yourself?
Good job, Taichi.
But it's nothing more than speculation right now. We don't have any actual proof.
So let's go to a love ho—
Quit screaming "love hotel"!
My mom is downstairs!
Kiriyama, you're screaming it, too.
Okay, fine. I'll go.
What?!
Score!
To school!
But I'm still really scared,
so...
If things start getting dangerous,
please stop me.
That's not what you're supposed to ask.
Something more like this.
"Please, protect me"?
It would be my honor.
Himeko?
Didn't your phone just ring?
Hey, you okay?
You've been acting pretty weird lately.
You're imagining things.
Yui!
Quit it, Iori.
Yui?
Yui, you're back!
I'm so glad!
Sorry to make you worry about me.
Worried sick!
Silly goose.
We didn't know if we should've visited or not!
Really? Sorry.
Oh, Kiriyama, you're back!
You're looking healthy.
Yes. Sorry I made you worry.
Hey, did you put on some weight?
You're imagining things!
Now if only Inaban would come to the club room.
That's a lot!
Isn't this a bit too much?
It was just supposed to be what we needed for the week,
but my desires got unleashed at the store...
My allowance for this month is all gone.
We can't really return it all now.
Aoki?
Hey, Aoki?
Give me those mitarashi dango!
An unleashed desire!
No!
These are mine!
Give me those mitarashi dango!
Looks like I got worried for nothing.
That's mine!
Wait, hold on, Nagase!
I just took a bite!
Get a different one!
I want that sandwich!
Not you, too, Kiriyama!
All three of you?
I guess it's a good thing it happened now. It's just—
Eat!
Give me that!
Morning, Inaba.
Um...
Don't worry about what you said to me the other day.
You shouldn't hold it against yourself.
Come back to the club room! We're all waiting for you!
See you!
Himeko, you have a visitor.
It's your teacher, Gotou-sensei.
Gotou?
You're not here to tell me it's over, are you?
It's still not over.
Were you browsing the internet?
So what if I was?
That's all you did back in middle school.
You were alone after school and on weekends.
Not trusting anyone.
Building walls around yourself.
Getting close enough to others so you could get through school without any problems,
but not close enough to call anyone a "friend."
Shut up.
I don't want to hear about that.
Just tell me what you're here for already.
Don't you remember, Inaba-san?
The last time I came,
I said that if things weren't interesting, I'd make them interesting.
Are you going to dump me in the river this time?
I thought you'd only interfere if we shut ourselves in.
Inaba-san, you're practically a shut-in now.
Like hell I am.
I'm going to school every day.
Just to stop me from interfering?
You really are very interesting, Inaba-san.
So what do you want?
You didn't come here for small talk.
Small talk?
You could call it that.
I just came here to shake things up.
Shake things up?
Yes.
You seem to be troubled right now.
Why do you feel so troubled?
Because of this "desire unleashing" bullshit that you're pulling.
No, I'm not talking about that.
Why is that place so important to you?
If you're tired of it, you could just destroy it.
Judging from your current mental state,
if you destroyed that place, you'd want to take the whole world out with it.
Or at least I hoped you would.
What the hell are you?
Is that place really the most important thing to you?
Huh?
Isn't there something in your heart that's just as important?
I don't know what you're talking about.
No, I'm right, aren't I?
You're trying so hard to pretend you don't know.
Because you might destroy that place if your feelings were found out.
You have someone very important to you.
Shut up!
Ah.
Looks like you know exactly what I'm talking about.
You can't go back now.
Once you've admitted it, you can't go back.
Oh?
I didn't think this would be so effective.
This looks like it will be very exciting.
How'd you like a fist to the face?
I'll just return this body to its owner before you hit me.
Are you going to do this to the others, too?
No need to worry.
This is a special visit just for you.
Don't you think something like this can be interesting as well?
How the hell could I?
And if you can use anyone's body, why didn't you use my family?
There aren't many people around who wouldn't mind a gap in their memory.
Don't shut yourself in any more now.
Yo.
Inaba!
Morning!
I was worried something might've happened since you're late.
There's no way I could stay home today.
I'm in charge of bringing vegetables, after all.
Let's go.
Fujishima'll get bitchy if we're late.
It feels like it's been a while since we talked like this.
I wonder how those three are doing.
Because if I didn't, we couldn't stay together!
Tell me! Tell me right now!
She found out! She found out! She found out!